Guide to the Kim Roberts biographical files of D.C. poets, 1995-2015 MS2222
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Kim Roberts biographical files of D.C. poets
1898-2015; undated.
1995-2015
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Roberts, Kim, 1961-
MS2222
4 Linear Feet
This collection contains programs, correspondence, articles and other miscellanies amassed by D.C. poet Kim Roberts pertaining to over 250 Washington D.C. poets.
Restrictions on Access
This collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Donated in 2007. Another donation in 2016. (Accession 2016.005)
Historical or Biographical Note
Kim Roberts is the editor of Beltway Poetry Quarterly and author of two books of poems, The Kimnama (Vrzhu Press, 2007), and The Wishbone Galaxy (Washington Writers Publishing House, 1994). Individual poems of hers are also included in numerous print anthologies, such as American Poetry: The Next Generation (Carnegie Mellon University Press), Cabin Fever (The Word Works, Inc.), Hungry As We Are (Washington Writers Publishing House), Poetic Voices Without Borders (Gival Press) and The First Yes: Poems About Communicating (Dryad Press), as well as CDs such as 31 Arlington Poets (Paycock Press) and Poetry Alive at Iota (Minimus Productions). She has published widely in literary journals throughout the US, as well as in Canada, Ireland, France, and Brazil.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains programs, correspondence, articles and other miscellanies amassed by D.C. poet Kim Roberts pertaining to over 250 Washington D.C. poets, invaluable to any researchers wishing to fully comprehend the D.C. poetry community or to obtain a glimpse of it and it's major players.
The collection is organized alphabetically by poet.
This collection is not yet processed, please see staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Arranged alphabetically.
Poetry; Washington (D.C.); Miller, E. Ethelbert
- Henry Adams (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Henry Adams, 1920-2014 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Kim Addonizio, 2005-2015 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Deborah Ager (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Deborah Ager, 2010 April 22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Karen LaLonde Alenier (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Karren Alenier, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Elizabeth Alexander (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Elizabeth Alexander, 2007-2015 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Kwame Alexander (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Kwame Alexander, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Lewis Alexander, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Fareedah Allah (Ruby C. Saunders), 2010 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Indran Amirthanayagam, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Cicely Angleton, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Francisco Aragon, 2010-2015 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Nancy Arbuthnot (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Barri Armitage (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Jennifer Atkinson (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Joseph Auslander, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Quiqne Aviles, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Joseph Awad (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Naomi Ayala (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Jonette Rose Barras (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Clara Barton, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Holly Bass (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Holly Bass, 2009-2015 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Sandra Beasley, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Richard Bausch (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Abby Beckel, 2011-2013 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Anne Becker (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Anne Becker, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Kimberly L. Becker, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Mel Berlin (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Mario Bencastro (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Rose Berger (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Donald Berger (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cliff Bernier (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Clifford Bernier, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Rei Berroa (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Reginald Dwayne Betts (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Reginald Dwayne Betts, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- R. Dwayne Betts, 2008-2013 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Ambrose Bierce (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Ambrose Bierce, 2010 April 22 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ambrose Bierce, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Elizabeth Bishop (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Star Black (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Star Black, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Richard Blanco (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Richard Blanco, 2003-2013 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Egla Mordles Blouin, 2010-2014 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Louise Bogan (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Jody Bolz (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Anne Lynch Botta, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Joseph Brodsky (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Gwendolyn Brooks (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Derrick Weston Brown (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Sterling Brown (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Sterling Brown, 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sterling A. Brown, 2008-2013 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Sarah Browning (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Sarah Browning, 2006-2011 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Carol Bruce
- Paula Closson Buck (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Linda Joy Burke (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Frances Hodgson Burnett (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Mary Burrill, 1942-2010 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- John Burroughs, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Forestine Bynum (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Regie Cabico, 2008-2015 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- James M. Cain, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Carmen Calatayud, 2004-2015 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Rick Cannon, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Helen Churchill Candee, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Rick Cannon (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Adelaide Cardozo, Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Nancy Naomi Carlson (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Kenneth Carroll (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Rachel Carson, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Grace Cavalieri (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Grace Cavalieri, 2008-2015 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Jennifer Chang, 2004-2014 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Alan Cheuse (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Lisa Chun (Box 1, Folder 43)
- George Churchill (Box 1, Folder 44)
- William Claire, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- John Clarke (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Vilena Lyons Clifton (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Michael Collier (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Billy Collins (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Billy Collins, Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Maxine Combs (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Geraldine Connolly (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Chris Conlon (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Anna Julia Cooper, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Cheryl L. Crockett (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Jane Alberdeston Coralin (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Teri Ellen Cross (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Maxine Combs, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- John Francis Cook, Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Donna Cowan, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Ed Cox (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Teri Ellen Cross (Davis), 2013 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Waring Cuney (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Waring Cuney, 1954-2012 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Roald Dahl, Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Gayle Danley (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Kyle Dargan, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Ann Darr (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Ann Darr, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Christina Daub (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Hayes Davis, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Michael C. Davis (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Eva Day (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Clarissa M. Scott Delany (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Joanna "Rocky" Delaplaine (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Joanne Rocky Delaplaine, Undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Peter Desmond (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Ramola Dharmary (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Joel Dias-Porter(aka DJ Renegade) (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Moshe Dor (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Rita Dove, 1995-2015 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Frederick Douglass (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Frederick Douglass, 2004-2012 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Rita Dove (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Alice Dunbar-Nelson, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Paul Lawrence Dunbar (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Paul Laurence Dunbar/Alice Dunbar-Nelson, 1898-1984 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Cornelius Eady (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Moira Egan (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Michele Elliott (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Thomas Sayers Ellis (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Thomas Sayers Ellis, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- John Elsberg (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Julie R. Enszer, 2011-2015 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Nora Ephron, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Danielle Evans, Undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Laura Fargas (Box 1, Folder 76)
- F. Scott Fitzgerald (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Roland Flint (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Yael Flusberg (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Calvin Forbes (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Carolyn Forche (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Donna Foulke (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Braudel France de Bravo, 2002-2008 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Jay Frazier (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Sunil Freeman (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Robert Frost (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Robert Frost, 2008-2014 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Heather Fuller (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Nancy Galbraith, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Martin Galvin (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Patricia Garfinkle (Box 1, Folder 88)
- David Gewanter (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Simki Ghebremichael (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Brian Gilmore (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Dana Gioia (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Linda Girardi (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Robert Girardi (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Robert L. Giron (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Louise Gluck (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Barbara Goldberg (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Manita Golden (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Patricia Gray (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Angelina Weld Grimke (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Michael Gushue (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Dan Gustein (Box 1, Folder 12)
- John Haines (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Donald Hall (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Monica Hand (Box 1, Folder 15)
- O.B. Hardison Jr. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Susan Shown Harjo (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Judith Harris (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Yona Harvey (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Anthony Hecht (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Hecht Galleys (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Isabel Likens Gates, Undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Bernadette Geyer, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Anne Kelledy Gilbert, Undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Brian Gilmore, 2009-2012 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Dana Gioia, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Louise Gluck, 2005-2014 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Angelina Weld Grimke, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Michael Gushue, 2011-2013 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Daniel Gutstein, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Robert Hass, 1995-2010 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Robert Herschbach, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Christopher Hitchens, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Tony Hoagland (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Andrew Holleran (Box 1, Folder 113)
- James C. Hopkins (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Ailish Hopper (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Ailish Hopper (Meisner), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Langston Hughes (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Langston Hughes (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Zora Neale Hurston (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Archibald MacLeish (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Tod Ibrahim (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Esther Iverem (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Reuben Jackson (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Josephine Jacobsen (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bernard Jankowski (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Randall Jarrell, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Philip K. Jason (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Valerie Jean (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Rod Jellema (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Rod Jellema, 2008-2011 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Paul Jennings, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Fred Joiner (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Georgia Douglas Johnson (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Nancy Johnson, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Edward P. Jones (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Edward P. Jones, 2009-2014 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Joy Jones, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- A. Van Jordan, 2002-2013 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Beth Joselow (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Beth Joselow, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Walter Karig, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Dolores Kendrick (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Dolores Kendrick, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- David Keplinger, 1994-2010 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Francis Scott Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Francis Scott Key, 1962-2013 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Alan King (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Clarence King, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Carolyn Kizer, 1992-2014 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Matthew Klam (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Peter Klappert (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Rosemary Klein (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Ann Knox (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Ted Kooser (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Ted Kooser, 2001-2014 (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Joyce Kornblatt (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Maxine Kumin, 1993-2014 (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Stanley Kunitz (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Stanley Kunitz, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Joe Lapp (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Hiram Larew (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Hiram Larew, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 88)
- Mary Ann Larkin (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Roger Lathbury, 2009-2015 (Box 5, Folder 89)
- Helen Elaine Lee (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Merrill Leffler (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Merrill Leffler, 2008-2015 (Box 5, Folder 90)
- Vladimir Levchev (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Philip Levine, 1988-2015 (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Lyn Lifshin (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Toni Asante Lightfoot (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Perry Lindstrom (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Alain Locke (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Alain Locke, Undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
- Robert Lowell (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Beverly Lowry (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Michael Lythgoe (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Saundra Rose Maley (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Thomas Mallon, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 93)
- William Matthews (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Steven Allen May, Undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
- C.M. Mayo (Box 2, Folder 38)
- C. M. Mayo, Undated (Box 5, Folder 95)
- David McAleavey (Box 2, Folder 39)
- David McAleavey, 1984-2005 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Greg McBride (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Melanie McCabe, Undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
- Richard McCann (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Judith McCombs (Box 2, Folder 42)
- W.S. Merwin (Box 2, Folder 43)
- W. S. Merwin, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 98)
- Ethelbert Miller (Box 2, Folder 44)
- E. Ethelbert Miller, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 99)
- Joaquin Miller (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Joaquin Miller, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- May Miller (Box 2, Folder 46)
- May Miller, 1995-2009 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Sami Miranda (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Samuel Miranda, Undated (Box 5, Folder 101)
- Honor Moore, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 102)
- Miles Davis Moore (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Miles David Moore, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 103)
- Sharon Morgenthaler (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Toni Morrison, 2003-2015 (Box 5, Folder 104)
- Kathi Morrison-Taylor (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Faye Moskowitz (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Elisabeth Murawski (Box 2, Folder 52)
- John Murillo, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 105)
- Gaston Neal (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Gaston Neal, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Yvette Neisser (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Tom Nicotera, 2010; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 106)
- Howard Norman (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Howard Norman, 2010-2013; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 107)
- Gloria Oden, Undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 108)
- Charles Olsen, 1950-1991; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 109)
- Elizabeth Oness (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Joe Osterhaus (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Sibbie O'Sullivan (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Kathleen O'Toole (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Kathleen O'Toole, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Kathleen O'Toole, Undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 110)
- Jose Emilio Pacheco (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Betty Parry (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Betty Parry, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Eric Pankey (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Linda Pastan (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Cissy Patterson, 2011; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 111)
- John Pauker (Box 2, Folder 64)
- John Pauker, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
- John Pauker, 2012; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 112)
- John Howard Payne (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Richard Peabody (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Richard Peabody, 2008-2012; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 113)
- Lisa Pegram (aka Lady Pcoq) (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Patric Pepper (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Patric Pepper, Undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 114)
- Christabelle Peters (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Leslie Pietrzyk (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Leslie Pietrzyk, 2009-2015; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 115)
- Albert Pike, Undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 116)
- Jon Pineda (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Robert Pinksy (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Robert Pinsky, 2008; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 117)
- Stanley Plumly (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Stanley Plumly, 2008-2013; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 118)
- Elizabeth Poliner (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Elizabeth Poliner, 2008; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 119)
- Esther Popel, Undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 120)
- Katherine Anne Porter (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Katherine Anne Porter, 2006-2009; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 121)
- Jacklyn Potter (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Ezra Pound (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Ezra Pound, 2008; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 122)
- Minnie Bruce Pratt (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Minnie Bruce Pratt, 2009; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 123)
- Dudley Randall (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Bernice Johnson Reagon (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Elizabeth Rees (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Joan Retallack (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Mary Roberts Rinehart (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Elisavietta Ritchie (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Elisavietta Ritchie, 2008-2013; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 124)
- M.L. Rosenthal, 1996-2012; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 125)
- Kay Ryan, 2005-2008; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 126)
- Carly Sachs (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Martha Sanchez-Lowery (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Robert Sargent (Box 2, Folder 88)
- M.A. Schaffner (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Gil Scott-Heron, 2012; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 127)
- Gregg Shapiro (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Gregg Shapiro, 2008-2012; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 128)
- Karl Shapiro (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Karl Shapiro, 2000; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 129)
- Jane Shore (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Susan Richards Shreve (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Malcolm Shute (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Charles Simic, 1982-2008; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 130)
- Myra Sklarew (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Myra Sklaren, 2003-2010; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 131)
- Dean Smith (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Katherine Smith (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Rod Smith (Box 2, Folder 98)
- E.D.E.N. Southworth (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Alan Spears (Box 2, Folder 10)
- A.B. Spellman (Box 2, Folder 11)
- A.B. Spellman, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- William Stafford (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Gary Stein (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Mark Strand, 1981-2013; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 132)
- Manil Suri, 2008-2009; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 133)
- Mark Tarallo (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Greg Tate (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Yermiyahu Ahron Taub, 2013; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 134)
- Henry Taylor (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Hilary Tham (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Susan Tichy (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Max Ticktin (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Jean Toomer (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Natasha Trethuewey, 2014-2015; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 135)
- Mark Twain, 1984-2010; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 136)
- Louis Untermeyer (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Elaine Upton (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Reetika Vazirani (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Mona Van Duyn (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Dan Vera (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Dan Vera, 2008-2011; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 137)
- Rebecca Villarreal (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Mark Wallace (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Robert Penn Warren (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Belle Waring (Box 2, Folder 119)
- Joshua Weiner (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Joshua Weiner, 2006; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 138)
- Edward Weismiller, Undated; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 139)
- Walt Whitman, 1988-2010; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 140)
- Reed Whittemore (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Reed Whittemore, 2007-2010; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 141)
- Richard Wilbur (Box 2, Folder 122)
- William Carlos Williams (Box 2, Folder 123)
- Rhonda Williford (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Terence Winch (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Rosemary Winslow (Box 2, Folder 126)
- Kathi Wolfe (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Kathi Wolfe, 2006-2010; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 142)
- Carter G. Woodson, 2006; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 143)
- Ernie Wormwood (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Charles Wright, 1982-2014; Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 144)
- Andrea Wyatt (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Elinor Wylie (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Elinor Wylie, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- A Sea Symphony (Box 2, Folder 131)
- WWQR (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Walt Whitman in Washington (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Walt Whitman in Washington (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Walt Whitman (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Brother Yao (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Ahmos Zu-Bolton (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Ahmos Zu-Bolton II, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Mary Kay Zuravleff (Box 3, Folder 7)